我叫Oliver Queen
My name is Oliver Queen.
被困在孤岛上5年以来
我只有一个目标...活下去
For 5 years,I was stranded on an
island with only one goal... survive.
Oliver Queen还活着
Oliver Queen is alive.
现在 我要完成我父亲的夙愿
Now I will fulfill my
father's dying wish...
根据他留给我的名单
除掉那些毒害我城市的人
to use the list of names he left me and
bring down those who are poisoning my city.
为了完成目标 我必须扮成别人
To do this,I must become someone else.
我必须掩盖身份
I must become something else.
绿箭侠 前情提要
Previously on "Arrow"...
我想让你和我一起调查义务警员
I'd like you to work with me
on the Vigilante investigation.
谢谢 长官
Thank you,sir!
这只是开始 六个月后
It's just beginning. In six months,
组织对城市的愿景就能实现了
the organization's vision of what
this city should be will be complete.
成千上万的无辜市民会死于非命
你却毫无感觉
Thousands of innocent people will
be dead and you'll feel nothing.
不对
That's not true.
我会有很有成就感
I'll feel a sense of accomplishment.
我们有什么可以帮忙的
So... How can we be of assistance?
我想让你们帮我杀了Malcolm Merlyn
Malcolm Merlyn. I want
you to kill him for me.
但这些黑箭不是他的作案手法
These black arrows aren't
consistent with his M.O.
有些事没法联系起来
Something doesn't add up.
直升机要降落了是什么意思
What do you mean,the
chopper's about to touch down?
飞行记录不允许再给他们20分钟
The flight log doesn't have
them due for another 20 minutes!
那就封锁停机坪
Then lock down the heliport!
我刚到斯特林市
I've just landed in Starling City.
我们说好抵达时一半
事成后再一半
We agreed... half on arrival,the
other half when the job is done.
总额
a***
谢谢 别担心 这个人...
Gracias. Don't worry.
The man's as good as...
Guillermo Barrera
Guillermo Barrera.
你让这座城市失望了
You have failed this city.
你名气可不小
You've built quite a reputation.
你本该在国外
And you should have stayed overseas.
我考虑过 但我想到我也不是吃素的
I thought about it,but then I
remembered... I've got a reputation,too.
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 看糖 旖旎 Ducky Rosemary
校对: Andrea942
时间轴:3p
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:3p
绿箭侠
第一季 第十六集
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
Arrow
Season 1 Episode 16
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
关键是你要让体重均匀分布
Now the trick is to keep your
weight evenly distributed.
我还以为是避免打架呢
I thought the trick was to
avoid getting into fights.
斯特林市可不是靠讲道理
就能摆脱麻烦的地方
Yeah,well,Starling City's where you can talk
not the kind of place your way out of trouble.
而且你如果想和我们一起干
Besides,if you're going
to be working with us,
要是能保护自己我就更放心了
至少会一点
I'll sleep a lot easier knowing that you
can handle yourself... At least a little bit.
怎么样
How'd it go?
- 他很不幸
- 谁不幸
- Badly for him.
- Who's him?
会用飞刀的雇佣杀手
An assassin for hire with
an affinity for knives.
- 他以前叫Guillermo Barrera
- 以前
- His name was Guillermo Barrera.
- Was?
那我们问不到他的目标了
So we can't ask him
about his intended target?
是的
No.
所以我需要你黑进他的手机
Which is why I need
you to hack his phone.
Barrera是世界级的
Barrera's world class.
他的目标都很高端
He kills high profile targets.
他被雇做的事还没完成
And whatever job he was
hired for isn't finished.
我们得找出他来这要杀谁 得快
We need to figure out who
he was here to kill,and fast.
他们也许还身处险境
They are probably still in danger.
- 行吗
- 好
- Ok?
- Yeah.
我要去见McKenna了
I have to meet McKenna.
还好你们没在停机坪碰到
Good thing she didn't
meet you at the heliport.
最好不要迷恋上一个要抓你的警察
May not be a good idea to fall for
the cop that's hunting you down.
这对我们义务警员来说可是不二选择
Well,it's slim pickings
for us vigilantes.
四个
Four.
我还是比较适合跑步
Well,I'm more of a runner.
为什么那么急着要健身
Why the sudden desire to work out?
不然还能做什么
What else is there to do?
我们可以想其他办法离开这个岛
Well,we can try to think of
another way off the island.
没有其他办法
There is no other way.
要是有我早想到了
If there was,I would have found it.
我们不能坐以待毙
We can't just sit here and wait
for Fyers to come and kill us.
我是有个想法
I did have one idea.
如果去树林里找足够多的竹子
If you go into the forest and gather
as much bamboo as you can find...
然后呢
Yeah?
我们就能造一个船 就像梦幻岛里一样
We could build ourselves a boat,like
they did on "Gilligan's Island."
这个坏了
That's broken.
坠机的时候摔坏了
It got busted during the crash.
你有试过修吗
Did you try to get it to work?
我更擅长拆东西
I'm better at pulling things apart.
我爸是飞行员 他经常自己修东西
My father was a pilot and he
used to do his own maintenance.
你觉得维修飞机还能遗传吗
So you're hoping aircraft
maintenance is genetic?
不是 我以前一直帮他
而且我也很喜欢
No,I used to help him and I liked it.
于是我就很擅长了
Then I got pretty good at it.
也许我能修好这个无线电
So maybe I can make the radio work.
你该为即将到来的战争训练自己
You should be training for the
inevitable fight that's looming.
我觉得我更有可能修好无线电
I think I have a better chance
of making the radio work.
抱歉我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
是我晚了 被困在了办公室
No,I am. I just got
caught up at the office.
我也是
Me,too.
你真漂亮
You look nice.
我们应该进去
We should go inside.
应该
We should.
我们不像是要进去的样子
We don't seem to be going inside.
欢迎
Welcome.
- 生日快乐 兄弟
- 谢谢
- Happy Birthday,buddy.
- Thank you.
这个像教皇新堡
Oh,this feels like a
Chateauneuf de Pape.
味道也像
It's going to taste like one,too.
真了解我 谢谢
You are a true friend. Thank you.
Tommy 你还记得McKenna Hall吧
Tommy,you remember McKenna Hall.
- 时光倒回
- 又回来了
- From back in the day.
- And back again.
Ollie
Ollie.
- Laurel 这是...
- McKenna Hall
- Laurel,this is...
- McKenna Hall.
我们在法庭上认识的
We know each other from the court house.
你好吗 律师
How are you,counselor?
我很好 警官
I'm well,Detective.
- 我要把这开了
- 进来吧
- I'm going to go crack this open.
- Come in.
好漂亮的房子 地方很大
Such a nice apartment. So much space.
这张好有爱
Oh,this is adorable.
你几岁的时候
How old are you here?
这其实是我妹妹Sarah
That's actually my sister Sarah.
噢 抱歉
Oh,I am so sorry.
不 没事
No,no,it's ok.
我不知道我爸为什么给她买金丝雀
I don't know why my father
bought her that canary.
这鸟整天叽叽喳喳 吵得我们快疯了
That thing chirped night
and day. Drove us all nuts.
干杯
A toast.
庆祝这么久以来我的第一个生日
To the first birthday that I
have enjoyed in a long time.
我最好的朋友回来了
I got my best friend back.
还有我终于知道为什么
And... I have finally figured out
why poets have been in business
诗人在过去几千年一直能立足
for the last few thousand years.
- 生日快乐 亲爱的
- 谢谢
- Happy Birthday,baby.
- Thank you.
干杯
Cheers. Cheers.
- 大概是外卖
- 好
- I think that's the food.
- Oh,ok.
幸亏她没做饭
Oh,thank God,she didn't cook.
是啊
Amen.
Merlyn先生
Mr. Merlyn.
Laurel 我能进来吗
Laurel. Can I come in?
Oliver
Oliver.
Merlyn先生
Mr. Merlyn.
我一直想联系你呢
I've been trying to
get in touch with you.
爸 你怎么来了
What are you doing here,Dad?
生日快乐 Tommy
Happy Birthday,Tommy.
我们单独谈谈
Just give us a second.
没问题
Of course.
- 我们准备吃饭了
- 我不久留
- We're about to eat.
- I can't stay.
那是 我没邀请你
Well,that works out
because you weren't invited.
我得到了斯特林市政集团的嘉奖
I'm being honored by the
Starling City Municipal Group.
他们授予我年度人道主义奖
They're bestowing me with
their annual Humanitarian Award.
怎么 他们没别人可授予了吗
What,they ran out of
actual humans to give it to?
如果可以我希望你能来
I would like you to
be there,if you could.
我确定我会很忙
I am 100% certain that I'll be busy.
你也许不会相信 我只是希望你快乐
You might not believe this,but all
I ever wanted for you was happiness.
如果这能缓和我们的关系
我还是会让它回到之前的状态
If it will allay this tension between
us,I'll turn the switch back on.
省着你的钱吧 老爸
Save your money,Dad.
我不会再需要了
I don't need it anymore.
我还是希望你能来参加这个活动
I'd still like you to come to the event.
这对我很重要
It would mean a lot to me.
知道吗 爸
You know what,Dad?
有时你最期待人 不会出现
Sometimes the people that you
want there the most... Aren't.
这是你教过我
You taught me that.
很多次的
Multiple times.
你好 Lawton
Hello,Lawton.
你的刀刃有点钝了
I see your edge has dulled.
我知道你在那儿
Oh,I knew you were there.
你是否要杀我 我不在乎
I just didn't care if you killed me.
你想怎么样
What do you want?
我们组织接了一单活儿
除掉某位高层人士
My organization has been contracted to
eliminate a certain high profile individual.
那家伙保镖环绕
A very well-guarded target.
别妄想了
Well,forget it.
我已退出江湖
Look,I'm retired.
就为了终日抽烟酗酒
To drink and smoke your life away?
总有一天 我们都会送命
We all got to die some time.
我需要某人死于最佳时机
I need someone to die at the right time.
再说 你的业务最强啊
And no one does it better than you.
我的视力 今非昔比了
My vision... ain't
exactly what it used to be.
不
No.
会好转的
It's going to be better.
要我干掉谁
So... Who needs two
bullets in the chest?
Moira
Moira.
是真的吗
Is it happening?
对
Yes.
人道主义奖颁奖礼上
The Humanitarian Award ceremony.
太公开化了点吧
Isn't that a little public?
没人会料到的
No one will expect it.
我有好消息跟大家分享
I have very welcome news
to share with all of you.
多亏Queen集团的应用科学部门
Thanks to Queen Consolidated's
Applied Sciences Division
以及他们近期对Unidac工业的收购
and their recent acquisition
of Unidac Industries,
我们定下的目标 只须几个月就可实现
the Undertaking which we set for
ourselves is only months from fruition.
对全市人来说 可以肯定的是
There's hope on the horizon
for everyone in starling.
我们不会让他们失望
We won't fail this city.
代表在座各位说一句
我们支持你 Malcolm
And I think I speak for everyone here
when I say we're all with you,Malcolm.
天呐 真是个偏执狂刺客
Jeez,this is one paranoid assassin.
Barerra的手机加密技术很高明
Barerra's got cobalt-level
encryption on his phone.
很难破解
It's not going to be easy to break.
但是 我小名叫破译者 其实是叫Megan
But codebreaker is my middle
name. Actually,it's Megan...
Felicity 你能挖出什么信息
Felicity,can you get anything off of it?
只有他最后拨打的号码
Just the last number he dialed.
- 打到哪里
- 唐人街的一个餐馆
- Which was?
- A restaurant in China town.
玉龙餐馆 杀手也爱吃我市最好的炒面
A Jade Dragon. I guess even hired
killers enjoy the city's best chow mien.
玉龙餐馆是中国黑帮的幌子
Yeah,Jade Dragon is a
front for the Chinese mafia.
打给餐馆 订一个今晚的两人桌
Call the restaurant,make a
reservation for two for tonight.
你得破解那部手机
You need to decrypt that phone.
我有点馋中餐了
I'm kind of in the mood for Chinese now.
这条鱼真大
That is...that is one big fried fish.
我听说这家川菜是本市最正宗的
I was told this was the most
authentic Szechwan in town.
我希望好好为你庆生
Whatever. I wanted to make sure that your
birthday celebration got its due celebration.
昨晚有点 拘谨
It was a little bit,um,tense last night.
都是因为我爸 气氛才不好的
Well,trust my dad to run all
the smiles out of the room.
他确实来过
貌似他努力想表现得像个老爸
He did come by,and it seemed like he
was trying to act a little bit dad-like.
像个老爸 真是对我爸的精辟概括
Dad-like,that sums up
my father perfectly.
我知道 你俩没完全闹僵
I know the two of you
have never been close,
但你母亲过世后 他也挺不容易的
but it couldn't have been easy
for him after your mom was killed.
别忘了 丧母的我也不易啊
Yeah,I guess he forgot that
there were two of us in that club.
我不是为他辩解 Tommy
I'm not defending him,Tommy.
只是 我也曾经历坎坷 痛失亲友
It's... With everything I've been
through,people that I've lost...
我知道那有多难过
I know how hard it can be.
你忘了吧
You probably don't remember this.
那时我们才八岁
We were eight.
我母亲下葬后 他消失达两年之久
But after her funeral,he
left for like two years.
回来后 他非常冷漠
And when he did come back,he
was... he was so frickin' cold.
我们几乎没有交流
We barely spoke.
所以我才会常去你家
And that's why I spent so
much time at your house.
表面看起来 我有父亲
From the outside,it always
looked like I had a father.
他给我钱花
我们住在一起 他来保释我
He paid my bills,he lived in
the house,he bailed me out.
但你爸爸带我玩了第一次曲棍球
But your dad took me
to my first hockey game.
你爸爸教我用假绳钓鱼
Your dad taught me how to fly fish.
你爸爸带我们
去看了第一场限制级电影
Your dad took us to
our first R-rated movie.
可他也非完人
but he wasn't perfect.
我爸也曾犯错
My dad made mistakes.
我们从未谈及此事
And... We haven't talked about this.
我对他有很多怒气
But I have a lot of anger towards him.
但我仍愿付出一切换他一命 因为...
But still,I would give anything
to have him back,because...
毕竟 他...还是你爸爸呀
At the end of the day,your
dad is... Your dad.
昨晚我说的是真心话
I meant what I said last night.
你回来了 我真的很高兴
I'm... really glad that you're back.
我去下洗手间
I got to hit the restroom.
黑帮正阴谋杀害某人
b***
告诉我是谁
c***
我没有替黑帮做事
d***
你可不是在这儿做点心的
e***
我不知道是谁
f***
但你肯定知道点什么
g***
跟我讲
h***
明天
i***
不论发生什么事 应该是在明天
j***
他是谁
k***
不知道 听他口音肯定是中国来的
(擦 这坑爹口音能是中国来的吗)
l***
买单
Check,please.
希望你爱吃烤肉
I hope you like barbecue.
不用太过感恩
Well,don't fall over
yourself thanking me
我在树上埋伏了6小时 给你弄了口吃的
for spending six hours
up a tree so you can eat.
你说啥
What?
很好 我一会儿吃
Great. I'll eat later.
你都鼓捣几天了 歇会儿吧
You've been on that for
days. Give it a rest.
我能弄好
It's because I can do this.
是啊 除非母猪会飞
Sure,kid. When pigs fly.
没开玩笑吧
You're kidding me.
声音能调清楚点吗
Can you clean this up?
不知道 我不知道是怎么做到这一步的
I don't know. I don't
know how I got this far!
继续靠近 大喷气机365
Continue approach. Big jet 365.
求救 求救 求救
Mayday,mayday,mayday.
我是楔子325
This is wedgetail 325.
飞行员和乘客已罹难
Pilot and passenger down.
2-7跑道就绪 有风 2-7-0度 风速10节
Runway 2-7 right,wind,2-7-0
degrees,10 knots.
重复一遍
飞行员和乘客已于炼狱岛罹难
I repeat...pilot and passenger
down on the island of Lian Yu.
请立即援救
Request immediate rescue.
可以着陆 2-7跑道就绪
Cleared to land,runway 2-7 right.
大喷气机365
Big jet 365.
他们听不见我们说话 我们没法呼救
They can't hear us,and
we can't call out.
我们仍是困兽
We're still trapped.
Lance
Lance.
黑帮雇了个职业杀手
The Triad have hired a contract killer.
是吗 你说停尸房那个
Yeah? You mean the one
you put in the morgue?
恭喜 你又成警察局的谈资了
Congratulations,you're the
talk of the station again.
他们雇了一个 就会再雇一个 探长
They hired one,they're going
to hire another,Detective.
知道会雇谁吗
Who's your target?
我在努力查 但没有线索
I'm trying to find out
but I'm hitting dead ends.
我希望你的人也着手调查
I need you to put your people on it.
我的人可不是你的手下
My people don't work for you.
对了 我也不是你的手下
And come to think of it,neither do I.
这不是你我之间的事 探长
It's not about you and me,Detective.
而是性命攸关的大事
It's about saving a life.
查出是谁了再打给我
Call me back when you got a name.
Hall
Hall.
有何吩咐 长官
Yes,sir?
你和我 我们去抓义务警员
You and me. We're going
to catch that Vigilante.
主楼层的5个出口都得堵死
There are five exit routes from the
main floor that need to be cut off.
一旦火警铃响 我们得在30秒内
Once the fire alarm goes
off,we'll have less than 30 seconds
解决掉Merlyn的贴身保镖
迫使他和人流一起出去
to disable Merlyn's private security
and force him outside with the others.
等他出去了
剩下的活儿 Lawton先生来干
Once he's outside... The
rest will be up to Mr. Lawton.
明白
Roger that.
拒绝访问
m***
好帅哦
You look handsome!
不是故意的 哥就是天生丽质嘛
I try not to. It just keeps happening.
干嘛去呀
What's the occasion?
去我爸的颁奖礼
I decided to go to my dad's thing.
真的
Really?
真的想好了
Are you sure?
差不多吧
Oh,mostly.
要我跟你一起去吗
Did you want me to go with you?
不用 不用 你忙你的吧
No,no,no,I know you have work to do.
我保证好好的
I promise I will be fine.
妈
n***
忽略
o***
你真美
You look beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
方便的话
我们可以在典礼之后一起进餐
If you're free,maybe after the ceremony,
聊一聊 就像以前那样
we could have dinner
and talk like we used to.
非常乐意
I'd like that.
我该走了
That's my cue.
整晚我都在躲着他
I've been trying to
avoid him all evening.
我们不出现才可疑
If we didn't show,it'd look suspicious.
你怎么能那么镇定
How can you talk to him that way?
跟没事人一样
As if nothing's about to happen?
我都这样五年了
I've been living this
life for five years.
再多五分钟没什么
Five more minutes won't matter.
女士们 先生们 晚上好
Good evening,ladies and gentlemen.
今天的获奖人无需多介绍
Now tonight's honoree needs
very little introduction.
撇开他的财富和名誉
It's neither his wealth nor his
name that we celebrate here tonight.
他为建造出更好的斯特林城
所付出的努力更为我们称道
But it is his efforts in making Starling
City a better and safer place to live.
一起来欢迎本年度
斯特林城的慈善家Malcolm Merlyn先生
So please help me welcome Starling City's
humanitarian of the year,Mr. Malcolm Merlyn.
那是个舞台
And so that's a stage,right.
一般晚上都会有乐队
Most nights we'll have a band.
很酷的那种
Fallout Boy乐队还流行吗
Somebody cool. Is
Fallout Boy still cool?
他们解散了
They broke up.
早就不流行了
And never.
还会有人再把乐队组起来的
So somebody else will pick the bands.
你有烦心事
Something bothering you?
别说没有 你撒谎技术太烂了
Don't say no,'cause
you're a terrible liar.
是吗
Really?
我还以为我技术进步了呢
I thought I was getting better at it.
怎么了
What's wrong?
生活中有好多事啊
There's a lot of stuff
going on in my life.
工作
Work.
朋友
Friends.
我正在艰难的思考适应所有的办法
And I'm having a... difficult time
figuring out how to fit it all in.
我对于那些也很纠结啊
I've been struggling with
some of those thoughts,as well.
有什么好主意吗
Do you have any good ideas?
我觉得坦诚对待生活就好
I think we just have to be really honest
about what's going on in our lives.
做得到吗
Think you can do that?
拜托啊
Come on.
进去啦 太好了
I'm in! Yes!
就是这样 Felicity Smoak
Yes! Yes,way to go,Felicity Smoak.
你不说西班牙语吧
You don't happen to
speak Spanish,do you?
阿拉伯语
Arabic.
唉
Oh,le sigh.
天啊
Oh,my God.
我在你身边啊
You know I'm there for you.
打扰一下 Queen先生
Excuse me,Mr. Queen.
信息技术部门有您要找的东西
The I.T. department has
that item that you requested.
- 稍等
- 好
- One sec.
- Ok.
你找到目标了
You find the target?
Oliver 目标是Tommy的爸爸
Oliver,the target is Tommy's father.
在颁奖典礼
At the awards ceremony?
Tommy在那
Tommy's there.
McKenna Diggle先生送你回家
Um,McKenna,Mr. Diggle is
going to take you home.
我突然有事
I have some unexpected business.
没关系
It's ok.
Lance
Lance.
目标是Malcolm Merlyn
Target is Malcolm Merlyn.
设好防线 保持距离
Establish a perimeter
but keep your distance.
我不希望警察介入
I don't want the police
caught in the crossfire.
我家真正的慈善家
是我的妻子Rebecca
The true humanitarian in the
Merlyn family was my wife Rebecca.
在座许多人都知道她
Many of you here knew her.
她不辞辛苦的致力于
帮助那些在林间不幸的人
She tirelessly devoted herself to helping
those less fortunate in the glades.
毫不夸张的说
假如有人想要谋杀她
I like to think that if the
men who murdered her knew her;
当他了解她的所作所为
knew the work that she did,knew
the person that she was...
肯定不会再偷她的钱包再杀了她
He would have helped her to
her car,made sure she was safe,
而会将她亲自送回车里
确保她的安全
instead of stealing her
purse and shooting her.
事实上 我为这座城市做的不够多
The truth is,I haven't
done enough for this city.
我的城市
My city.
我辜负了它
I failed it.
但我保证 我还会继续
But I promise you...
I am not finished yet.
我保证 这座城市会变得更好
I promise you that this city
will be better for all of us.
到那一天 再看到这个华丽的奖杯
我会感到名之所至
And on that day,I will look at this beautiful
award and feel that I have earned it.
谢谢大家
I thank you.
Tommy
Tommy!
Merlyn没上钩 改变计划
Merlyn's not taking the
bait. Change of plans.
我讨厌临时改计划
I don't like improvisation.
让他上楼 去他屋顶的办公室
Drive him upstairs to
his penthouse office.
我需要到有利的地方去
I need to switch vantage points.
Tommy
Tommy!
跟我来
Come with me.
二楼有一个出口
There's an exit on the second floor.
你安全了我再走
I wasn't leaving until
I knew you were safe.
去安全的地方 我会拖住他们
Go somewhere safe. I'll hold them off.
- 快走
- 走吧
- Go now!
- Come on!
- 去哪
- 上楼
- Where are we going?
- Up.
- 他们是谁
- 不知道
- Who are those guys?
- I don't know.
他们想杀你
They're trying to kill you!
似乎是
Seems that way.
我们就这么不带保镖自己上楼吗
And we're going up,without
any of your bodyguards?
爸 我们得离开这里
Dad! We need to get out of here.
Tommy 深呼吸 相信我
Tommy,take a deep breath and trust me.
我楼上的办公室是间安全房
Upstairs in my office is a panic room.
我们到了那 就关上门
We get there,we seal it off.
Merlyn在往顶层走
Merlyn's headed to the penthouse.
为什么要杀Malcolm Merlyn
Why do you want Malcolm Merlyn dead?
杀你也行
I'll settle for you.
等等
Wait!
- 走
- 你杀了他
- Go!
- You killed him!
因为他可能会杀你
Surely as he would have killed you.
走 走 快走
Move,move,move!
电磁闭锁
Electromagnetic locks.
要是他们关了电源呢
What if they cut the power?
这层楼是完全独立的输电网
This floor is on an
entire separate grid.
万一打碎玻璃呢
The glass?
聚碳酸酯的 防弹的 没事了
Lexan. Bulletproof. It's over.
你怎么会的
How did you know how to do that?
什么
What?
打人
Fight.
杀人
Kill.
爸
Dad?
不许动 斯特林市警察
Freeze! SCPD.
把弓放下
Put the bow down.
Tommy 你还好吗
Tommy,you ok?
爸
Dad!
Dad?!
慢慢转过身来
Turn around slowly.
爸
Dad.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我没事
I'm ok.
没事
靠
Damn it.
你在流血啊
You're bleeding. You're bleeding.
我没事的 Tom
I'll be fine,Tom.
不要啊 爸
No,no,no,Dad!
别过来
No!
退后
Stay back.
我不是来伤害你或者你爸爸的
I'm not here to hurt you or your father.
我说了退后
I said stay back.
是箭毒
Curare.
别再靠近了
Don't come any closer.
你爸中毒了
Your father's been poisoned.
一名叫Floyd Lawton的刺客
把他的子弹涂上了箭毒
An assassin named Floyd Lawton
laces his bullets with curare.
我以前处理过这种
I've dealt with this before.
我们需要稀释他血液里的毒
We need to dilute the
poison in his bloodstream.
我让你往后退
I said stay the hell back!
3分钟内他会失去知觉
In three minutes he's paralyzed.
4分钟内他会窒息而亡
In four minutes,he suffocates.
如果你不让我帮你
不用等其他人赶来他就死了
If you don't let me help you now,he's
dead before anybody gets here!
帮我 怎么帮
Help. How?
新鲜的血液可以让他挺到医院
Fresh blood buys him time
to get to the hospital.
输血吗
A blood transfusion?
太荒唐了
That's insane!
这是唯一的方法
It's the only way.
他需要你输血
He needs your blood.
没时间了
You're out of time.
你必须现在做决定
You need to make a decision right now.
我为什么要相信你
Why should I trust you?!
因为你一直如此
Because you always have.
Oliver
Oliver.
准备好了吗
Ok. Ready?
开始吧
Do it.
托住他的胳膊
Hold his arm.
加油 加油 加油
Come on,come on,come on.
你是义务警员
You're the Vigilante.
为什么
Why?
以后再说
Later.
他还需要住院治疗
He's still going to
need medical attention
才能完全清除血液里的毒液 明白吗
to fully clean out his
system,you understand?
嗯
Ok.
谢谢
Thank you.
Tommy
Tommy.
我在这 爸
I'm right here,Dad.
帽衫男跟你说什么了
What did the Hood say to you?
什么都没说
He didn't say anything.
你听信一个杀人狂进行现场输血
You let a homicidal maniac talk you
into a homemade blood transfusion
而不是呼叫医务人员
instead of calling the paramedics?
我父亲的生命危在旦夕
My father's life was at stake.
帽衫男先是从绑匪手里救了你和Queen
So first the Hood rescues you
and Queen from those kidnappers,
现在他又救了你父亲
now he saves your old man.
但他又不遗余力地扳倒其他大人物
But he's taking down every
other one percenter out there.
难道说他是你的朋友 Merlyn
Is this guy a friend of yours,Merlyn?
我根本不认识他
I don't know who the hell he is.
如果他们听不见我们说话
那这又有什么用呢
If they can't hear
us,then what's the point?
等等
Wait!
可能还是有点用
You still might have done us some good.
凌晨5点离开我的坐标
0500 hours from my mark.
终极部署准备就绪
Final deployment is five by five.
那是Fyers
That's Fyers!
我将频率调到了部队的波段
I'm tuned into the soldier's frequency.
Scylla正在路上 预计早上6点抵达
Scylla is in route. ETA 0600 hours.
在西南海湾
At the southwest bay.
Scylla就位后联系你
I'll call you when Scylla
is in my possession.
Fyers出发了
Fyers out.
Fyers在跟谁说话
Who was Fyers talking to?
不知道
I don't know.
听起来不像是岛上的人
说不定是他的雇主
Sounds like someone off this
island,maybe his benefactor.
更关键的是 Scylla是什么
More importantly,who or what is Scylla?
Scylla和Charibdis
The Scylla and Charibdis.
是奥德赛里的人物
那章讲述了四大噩梦之一
It's "The Odyssey," from one
of the four nightmare chapters.
Scylla是个怪物
Scylla was a monster.
我想会会这个怪物
I want to meet this monster.
一起去吗
Am I going alone?
救了个大人物 感觉怎么样
So how's it feel to
save a one percenter?
看起来Malcolm Meryln没什么大碍
Looks like Malcolm
Meryln's going to be ok.
他们把他送到了斯特林市总医院
They took him to Starling General.
还好他穿了防弹背心
Good thing he was wearing
a bulletproof vest.
他不是因为枪伤才进的医院
He's not in the hospital
because he was shot.
他被箭毒所伤
He was poisoned by curare.
Lawton还活着
Lawton's alive.
抱歉 John
I'm sorry,John.
这个Lawton找过他麻烦吗
This Lawton kick his dog or something?
没
No.
他杀了John的哥哥
He killed his brother.
什么
What?
那是什么
What is it?
你说对了
You were right.
Scylla确实是个大怪兽
Scylla is a monster.
俄罗斯S300防空导弹发射台
A Russian-made S300
anti-aircraft missile launcher.
它可以同时追踪100个目标
至少命中1打
It can simultaneously track up to a hundred
targets while engaging with at least a dozen.
我是说 从这他们可以击落一驾商用客机
甚至于挑起一场战争
I mean,from here,they could shoot down
a commercial airliner,or start a war.
你来了啊
Hey,you're here.
跟我来
Walk with me.
我听说你在事发现场 你还好吗
I heard you were there,are you ok?
我很好
I'm fine. Fine.
听着 McKenna 我...
我很抱歉当时匆忙离开了
Listen,McKenna,I'm... I'm really sorry
that I had to run out on you like that.
没关系 5分钟之后 我也得走了
Don't worry. Five more minutes,and
I would have had to run out on you.
我们的生活都不简单
Our lives are complicated.
尽管如此 如果你愿意的话
But I'm willing to figure us out.
我还是愿意确定我们的关系
If you are.
我很乐意并且能做到
Willing and able.
爸爸
Hey. Hey,Dad.
放轻松
Take it easy.
你中枪了
You were shot.
子弹上有毒
The bullet was laced with poison.
我怎么没死
I should be dead.
我给你输了血
I gave you a blood transfusion.
事实上...是义务警员的主意
Actually it was... the Vigilante's idea.
他救了你
He saved you.
是吗
He did?
我好害怕就这样失去你
I was worried I was going to lose you.
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
妈妈死了之后 你也是这样说的
You said that after mom died.
但你还是走了
But you left.
你妈妈死了之后
我没有尽到父亲的责任
I wasn't a very good father to
you after your mother passed away.
我当时好迷茫
I was so lost.
你从没告诉过我 你去哪了
You never told me where you went.
我到了一个叫Nanda Parbat的地方
I found myself in a
place called Nanda Parbat.
在那我遇到了一个人
I met a man there.
他让我对事物有了新的认知
He helped me make sense of things.
他让我找到了人生的目标
He helped me to find
a purpose for my life;
让大家感觉这个城市更加美好
to make this city a
better place for everyone.
尤其是你
Especially for you.
你打算怎么做
How are you going to do that?
Malcolm
Malcolm?
Tommy
Tommy.
我可以和Moira单独谈一下吗
Could I talk to Moira for a minute?
谢天谢地 你还活着
Thank God you're all right.
我们中有个叛徒
We have a traitor in our midst.
你去把他找出来
I want you to find out who.
他大错特错了
He just made his last mistake.
我爸爸没事 多亏了你
My dad's going to be ok,thanks to you.
多亏你自己
It's thanks to you.
我曾经问过你 在岛上发生了什么
No one's asked you what happened
to you out on that island.
- 你说"很多" 这说不通
- Tommy
- You said "a lot." That doesn't quite cover it.
- Tommy...
我亲眼看见你杀了绑架我们的那些人
就在你刚回来那时 我没有看错吧
I saw you kill those guys who kidnapped
us when you first got back,didn't I?
我...我知道你有很多疑问
I... I know you have a lot of questions.
是
Yeah.
但是现在 我只想知道
Yeah,but for now,just the one.
你有没有打算告诉我发生了什么
Were you ever going to tell me?
没
No.
Tommy 我在新闻上都看到了
Tommy,I just saw it all on the news.
我马上赶过去
I'll be there as soon as I can.
拜
Bye.
嗨 Laurel
Hello,Laurel.
妈妈
Mom?
你来这做什么
What are you doing here?
我想跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
谈什么
About what?
我知道我错了
I know I've made mistakes.
是
Yeah.
是 你错了
Yes,you have.
听着 我要走了
Look,I have to go.
不如你给我写个邮件或者明信片什么的
Why don't you send me an
email or a postcard some time?
我有重要的事情要和你谈谈
I have something important
I need to discuss with you.
都过去这么久了 还有什么是重要的
What could be so important
after all this time?
关于Sarah
It's about Sarah.
她怎么了
What about her?
我想她可能还活着
I think she may be alive.
--------------------------
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负
--------------------------
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 看糖 旖旎 Ducky Rosemary
校对: Andrea942
时间轴:3p
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:3p
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo